Contact

7878571228 (Mobile) rutvikraval88@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rutvik-raval-04617b199 (LinkedIn) rutvik-portfolio.vercel.app/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Flutter Java MySQL

Rutvik Raval

Senior Flutter Application Developer Gujarat, India

Summary

Am a skilled Mobile Developer who has around 3 years of experience with Flutter Hybrid Mobile App development. If looking for a highly skilled and rich experienced mobile expert with a deep knowledge, a professional attitude, excellent communication skills and the highest code quality, In addition, promise to always honest of work.

I'm based in Surat, India. I'm passionate about improving the lives of others through mobile app and i am constantly looking to learn new things everyday.

√# completed many projects like organization-related, educationrelated, and social media apps.

√# Integrate chat module with audio, files

✓# Payment Integration (Stripe, Paypal, RazerPay)

√# Working with Firebase

√# Knowledge of application deployment in Google Play Store and App Store

√# Knowledge of Architecture Pattern design(MVVM, MVC, and MVP)

√# Working with State management (Provider, Getx, BLoC), etc.

Skills:

Flutter, Dart, BLoC,GetX
Java, Kotlin, C++,
PHP MySQL, SQLite, SQL Server, HTML

Tools:

Xcode, Android Studio, GitHub VS code, etc

Experience

Primeval Technologies Inc

5 months

React Js Developer

May 2023 - Present (3 months)

Flutter Developer

March 2023 - Present (5 months)

√# Working with Firebase

√# Knowledge of application deployment in Google Play Store and App Store

√# Knowledge of Architecture Pattern design(MVVM, MVC, and MVP)

√# Working with State management (Provider, Getx, BLoC), etc.

UPQOR

Flutter Developer

December 2021 - April 2023 (1 year 5 months)

Gujarat, India

√# completed many projects like organization-related, education-related, and social media apps.

√# Integrate chat module with audio, files

√# Payment Integration (Stripe, Paypal, RazerPay)

√# Working with Firebase

✓# Knowledge of application deployment in Google Play Store and App Store

√# Knowledge of Architecture Pattern design(MVVM, MVC, and MVP)

√# Working with State management (Provider, Getx, BLoC), etc.

Keron infotech

Flutter Developer

January 2020 - October 2021 (1 year 10 months)

Gujarat, India

√# Working with Firebase

√# Knowledge of Architecture Pattern design(MVVM, MVC, and MVP)

√# Working with State management (Provider, Getx, BLoC), etc.

Education

Veer Narmad South Gujarat University, Surat

B.C.A, Computer and Information Sciences, General · (January 2017 - June 2020)